Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Students Records, 1907-2015: Finding Aid AC136
University Archives
- Series 1: Administrative, 1907-2001; 31 boxes; 2 items
  - First Year Questionnaires, 1988-2001; 2 boxes
    - Participants' Grade Point Averages, 1988; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Participants by Class, 1996 July 2; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Transition (Evaluation), 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Freshman Summer Orientation Program Evaluations, 1997; 1 box
      - Group Leaders, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 28)
      - Program Planning, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 29)
      - Summary, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 30)
      - Training and Reception Speech, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 31)
      - Release Forms, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 32)
      - Program/Schedule, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 33)
      - Participants/Leaders, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 34)
      - Administration/Financial, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Senior Thesis - Benjamin Sommers, 2000 April 3; 1 folder (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Neil L. Rudenstine Correspondence, 1969-1970; 1 box
    - A-B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - C-D, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - E-F, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - G-I, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - J-L, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - O-R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - S-V, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - W-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Memos to and from President Goheen, 1956-1970; 2 folders (Box 26, Folder 9-10)
  - John Danielson Correspondence, 1966-1970; 1 folder (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Subject Files, 1959-1974; 1 box
    - Administrative Assistants, 1968-1970; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - ACTION, 1969; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Student Payroll, 1972; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Undergraduate Assembly, 1971; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Luncheon, 1971 January 15; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Council of the Princeton University Community, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Fires, 1971; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Parietals, 1968; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Clubs, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Bicker, 1968; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Campus Disruption, 1968; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Personnel, 1972-1974; 1 box
      - Turner, Debbie, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 12)
      - Tippett, Louise, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 13)
      - Barbara Hill, 1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 14)
      - Jones, Jesse, 1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 15)
      - Boehlke, Steven, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 16)
      - Aguilar, Glenn, 1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Trustees, Board of, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Married Undergraduates, Butler Tract, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Married Students, 1964-1972; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Early Coeducation, 1969-1973; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Early Coeducation, Surveys (Sealed), circa 1973; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 22)
      Restricted until 2048
    - Pet Policy, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 23)
    - Undergraduate Student Life, 1967; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 24)
    - Drugs, 1967-1970; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 25)
    - Stevenson Hall, 1971; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 26)
    - Hickel Incident, 1970; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 27)
    - Hickel Hearings, 1970 March 16-30; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 28)
    - Huey Newton Affair, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - Rhodes Scholarship, 1971; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - Dean of Students General Information, 1960-1963; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - Campus Revolt, 1967-1969; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - James B. Laughlin Correspondence, 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 27, Folder 33)
  - Housing, 1969-1977; 1 box
    - Stevenson Hall, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Princeton Inn, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Flood Damage, 1975; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Undergraduate Life Committee, 1977 February 28; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - CHRONO, Ellen Porter, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Stevenson Hall, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - CHRONO, Ellen Porter, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Rooms in New-New Quad, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Minority Student Housing, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Fuel Shortage, 1973; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Coed Bathrooms, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - Housing Office Policy/Proposals/Press/Fall Housing, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - Housing (General), 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - Residence Committee, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - Mailing to Incoming Students, 1971-1970; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - Tom Root - Memos, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - Housing Survey Princeton, 1970; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - Gauss Kitchen Suite, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - Wilson College, 1970-1973; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - Colleges, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - Sophomore Groups: Memos, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - Transfers, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - Wilson College, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - Room Draw, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - Dining Contracts - Policies and Exempts, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - Student Housing, 1972-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - Transfers, Readmits, 1975-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - Housing - Policies, 1974-1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - Visiting Students, Spring, 1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - Housing Margin, 1970; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Student Housing Cooperative, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Second Means of Egress, Housing, 1975-1977; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Storage Policy, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Room Draw, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - John Hlafter, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Holden - Bathrooms etc, 1972-1974; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Arrangements for Coed Housing, Parietals etc, 1972; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Housing Margin, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Dorm Occupancy Review, 1971-1974; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Dormitory and Food Services Problems, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Housing, Spring, 1973; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Housing, General, University Guests (Palmer House), 1976; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Commons (and Sophomore Release Programs), 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 28, Folder 43)
  - Princeton Inn College, 1969-1973; 1 box
    - Princeton Inn College Residence Matters, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Princeton Inn, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Princeton Inn College Newsletters, Etc, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Princeton Inn College, 1972-1973; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Princeton Inn Memos, Early Planning, 1969-1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Princeton Inn College Recruiting, 1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Princeton Inn College Annex Rooms, 1973; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Albert Sonnenfield, Master of Princeton Inn College, 1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Princeton Inn College Planning for First Year, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Princeton Inn College, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Princeton Inn College, 1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Housing Matters, Spring-Summer, 1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Undergrad Announcement Write-Up, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Drugs, undated; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Staff - West College, Infirmary, Counseling Center, 1974-1975; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Fraternities, 1975; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Co-op Houses / Coed Suites, 1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Dorm Council, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - Shockley-Innis Debates, 1971-1973; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - Tiger Paws (Inactive), 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - Tiger, the Princeton, 1962-1968; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - Triangle Club, 1965-1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - Undergraduates for a Stable America, 1970; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - Whig Hall Fire, 1969 November; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - "A Report on Woodrow Wilson Lodge", 1960; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - Association of Black Collegians, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - Summer in Engineering, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - Family Sponsors, 1969; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - Recommendations, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - Harold Stassen, 1948; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - Miscellaneous Forms, 1959; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - Business Today, 1969-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - Grading and Policy, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Undergraduate Officers, 1969; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - Triangle Club Trustees, 1965-1968; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - Undergraduate Life Space Study, 1970-1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Classes of, 1972-1973; 1969-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Class Finances, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Huey Newton Speech, 1971; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Activities Board, 1970-1971; 2 folders (Box 29, Folder 40-41)
  - Dormitory Council, 1969; 1 folder (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous Student Data Sheets, 1972; 2 folders (Box 29, Folder 43-44)
  - Miscellaneous Reports, 1970; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Classes and Services Financial Statements, 1971-1972; 5 folders (Box 30, Folder 2-6)
  - International Students, 1982-1995; 1 box
    - Class of, 1985; 1983-1985; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 7)
      [restricted until 2060]
    - Aboah, Sam, 1985; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Class of, 1986; 1982-1986; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 9)
      [restricted until 2061]
    - Class of 1987, 1983-1987; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 10)
      [restricted until 2062]
    - Mitra, Samir, 1987; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Class of, 1988; 1985-1988; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 12)
      [restricted until 2063]
    - Class of, 1989; 1985-1989; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 13)
      [restricted until 2064]
    - Class of, 1995; 1991-1995; 1 folder (Box 30, Folder 14)
      [restricted until 2070]
  - Princeton Inn, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Coeducation, 1973-1974; 2 folders (Box 31, Folder 2-3)
  - Committee on Residential Life, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Colleges and Halls, 1972; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Dean Simmons, 1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Community Relations, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Institute for Defense Analyses, 1970-1972; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Ivy Athletics, 1976-1977; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Women at Princeton, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Golda Meir, 1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Concerned Alumni of Princeton and Prospect, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Cohabitation, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Computer Center, 1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Energy Crisis, 1973-1974; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - John Doar, 1975; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Stevenson Hall, 1971-1972; 1 folder (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Series 1: Administrative, undated; 1 item
- Series 2: Student Activities and Organizations, 1940-1997; 16 boxes; 1 folder
  The Student Activities and Organizations series contains records of the many extracurricular activities initiated by Princeton undergraduates over the years. The records consist largely of charters and financial accounts submitted to the Office of the Dean of Students for approval.
  The arrangement of the records at the time of transfer has been retained. Generally, records pertaining to student-led organizations are in several rough chronological groupings, and are filed alphabetically thereunder. Records pertaining to the Reserve Officers Training Corps, Eating Clubs, and Outdoor Action program are grouped together elsewhere in the series.
  - 1952-1970, 2 boxes
    - Hillel Foundation, 1961-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - History of Ideas Club, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Informed Citizens Against Apathy, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Institute of Aeronautical Sciences, 1959-1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - The Institute of Electrical and Electronic Engineers, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - International Affairs Council (International Relations Club), 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Amateur Radio Society, 1956-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Symposium on World Affairs, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Rifle Team, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Right Wing Club, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Rocky Mountain Empire Club, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Rugby Club, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Russian Club, 1964 February; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - St. Louis Club, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - St. Photius (Greek Orthodox) Foundation, 1962-1964; 2 folders (Box 32, Folder 15-16)
    - Savoyards, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Scranton for President, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Semper Fidelis (Marine), 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - The Shades (Rock 'n Roll), 1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Ski Club, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Spanish Club, 1961-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Sports Car Club, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Princeton Review, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Princeton Sport Diving Club, 1965 March; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Princeton Theater Workshop, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Princeton University Concert Jazz Band,1964, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Pro Musica, Princeton, 1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Radical Action Group (R. A. G.), 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Sports Car Club, 1952-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Stock Investments and Analysis Club, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Engineering Council, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Evangelical Fellowship, 1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Flying Club, 1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Footnotes, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - French Club, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - German Club, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Glee Club, 1962-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Go Club, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - Good Timers (Guide to Women's Colleges), 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - Barn Dance Club, 1961-1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 41)
    - Basic Engineering Society, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 42)
    - Princeton Bible Study Group, 1963-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 43)
    - Bicycle Team, 1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 44)
    - Bipartisan Society, 1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 45)
    - Bric-A-Brac, 1962-1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 46)
    - Bridge Club, 1962-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 47)
    - Brink (Student Peace Union), 1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 48)
    - Cabaret, 1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 49)
    - Campus Fund Drive, 1966-1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 50)
    - Campus News Magazine, 1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 51)
    - Cane Spree (Freshman-Sophomore Rivalry), 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 52)
    - Car Rental Agency, 1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 53)
    - Catalyst, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 55)
    - Chapel Choir, 1963-1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 56)
    - Chapel Deacons, 1961-1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 57)
    - Princeton International Law Society, 1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 58)
    - Intime, Summer, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 59)
    - International Students Association, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 60)
    - Intramural Athletic Association, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 61)
    - Investors Club, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 62)
    - Islamic Society of Princeton, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 63)
    - Jaycees, 1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 64)
    - Jazz at Princeton, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 65)
    - Jolly Rogues, 1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 66)
    - Judo Club, 1962-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 67)
    - Karate Club, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 68)
    - Libertarian Society, 1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 69)
    - Memorial Fund Drive, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 70)
    - Princeton Motorcycle Scrambling Club, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 71)
    - Cheerleaders, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 72)
    - Chess Club, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 73)
    - Daily Princetonian - Civil Rights, 1963-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 74)
    - Christian Science Organization, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 75)
    - Circle K Club of Princeton, 1962-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 76)
    - Commons, 1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 77)
    - Princeton University Student Chapter of the Association for Computing Machinery, 1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 78)
    - Concordia Society (Lutheran), 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 79)
    - Conservative Club, 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 80)
    - Counterrevolutionary League, 1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 81)
    - Committee for Racial Reconciliation, 1964; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 82)
    - Da Camera Violin and Piano Duo, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 83)
    - Notices to Daily Princetonian, 1963-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 84)
    - Daily Princetonian Award, 1963-1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 85)
    - Debate Panel, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 86)
    - Debate Panel Funds, 1967-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 87)
    - Democratic Club, 1961-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 88)
    - Deseret Club (Mormon), 1960-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 89)
    - Jim Dashow Quartet, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 90)
    - Draft Resistance Union, Princeton, 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 91)
    - Ecology Action, 1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 92)
    - The Princeton Engineer, 1963-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 93)
    - Extra Curricular (General), 1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 94)
    - ABC (Association of Black Collegians), 1969-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 95)
    - Ad Hoc Committee for Negotiations in Vietnam, 1966-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 96)
    - Advertising Forum, 1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 97)
    - African Affairs Committee, 1961-1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 98)
    - Agency Council, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 99)
    - Alpha Phi Omega, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 100)
    - American Field Service, 1964-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 101)
    - American Institute of Architects, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 102)
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 103)
    - American Institute of Electrical and Radio Engineers, 1962-1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 104)
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 105)
    - American Society of Civil Engineering, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 106)
    - American Society of Mining Engineers, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 107)
    - Americans for Reappraisal of Far Eastern Policy, 1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 108)
    - Anchor and Chain Society, 1960-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 109)
    - Aquinas Foundation, 1960-1961; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 110)
    - Arabic Club, 1964-1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 111)
    - Archery Club, 1961-1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 112)
    - Arnold Air Society, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 113)
    - Arts at Princeton, 1965-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 114)
    - Association Internationale des Estudiantes en Sciences Economiques et Comerciales (AISEC) International Conference, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 115)
    - AISEC, 1963-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 116)
    - Association of Latin Collegians, 1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 117)
    - Band, 1963-1970; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 118)
    - Pre-Medical Society, 1964-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 119)
    - Press Club, 1966-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 120)
    - Princeton Brass Ensemble, 1964; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 121)
    - Princeton Entertainment Bureau, Inc, 1962; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 122)
    - Princeton Folk Music Society, 1965-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 123)
    - Princeton Group for Human Rights, 1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 124)
    - Princeton Mountaineering Club, 1965; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 125)
    - Nassau Literary Magazine, 1963-1968; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 126)
    - Nassoons, 1962-1967; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 127)
    - Omicron Delta Esilon, 1964-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 128)
    - Orchestra, Princeton University, 1962-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 129)
    - Outing Club, Princeton (P. O. C.), 1955-1970; 2 folders (Box 32, Folder 130-131)
    - Palmer Square Hockey Club, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 132)
    - Pan-African Student Organization of the Americas, 1963; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 133)
    - Photography Club, 1964-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 134)
    - Pistol Club, 1962-1966; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 135)
    - Pre-Law Society, 1968-1969; 1 folder (Box 32, Folder 137)
  - 1970-1982, 1970-1986; 2 boxes
    - Careers in Social Change Program, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Student Organizations, Coordination of, 1971-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Accion Puertorriquena, 1975-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - African Students Union, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Princeton Alliance to Reverse the Arms Race, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Alliance of the Third World Women, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Alpha Omega Fellowship, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - American Field Service, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - American Society of Civil Engineers, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Amnesty International, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Arch Angels, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Armenian Students of Princeton University, 1980-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Archery Club, 1976-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Asian-American Student Association, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Princeton Art, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Student Friends of the Art Museum, 1974-1980; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Princeton Badminton Club, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - Balloon Club, 1980-1981; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - Princeton Baha'i Club, 1980; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - Band Half-Time Shows, 1981-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - Princeton University Band, 1973-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - Society of Black Architects, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - Bowling Club, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - Princeton Bridge Club, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - Bric-A-Brac, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - Campus Fund Drive, 1979-1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Cambodian Family Committee, 1982; 1 folder (Box 33, Folder 28)